asb.tv 2011-12-27

# Airshowbuzz.com: Your Aviation Resource

**We know people rarely read the fine print, but we thought we’d post it anyway. Without breaking out your magnifying glass, we’ll zealously guard your personal information and we’ll never compromise your integrity, or ours.**

**Last Updated: 11.7.08**

**1\. Policy**

Airshowbuzz, LLC ("ASB") has created this privacy policy (the “Policy”) to explain our privacy practices so that you will understand when and how personal information is collected, used, disclosed and protected with respect to this website (the "Site"). ASB respects the privacy of its users, and this Policy explains what information we collect on our Site and how we use such information. Please read this Policy carefully. In addition, please review the [Rules of Engagement](http://www.airshowbuzz.com/rules.php) posted at the Site, which governs your use of the Site. Your use of our Site indicates to us that you have read and accepted our privacy practices, as outlined in this Policy.

**2\. Applicability**

Please note that this Policy only applies to this Site and any other site owned and/or operated by or for ASB upon which ASB has placed a "link" which, when "clicked," transfers you to this Policy. This Policy only covers information collected at this Site, and does not cover any information collected by any other site unless otherwise specifically stated or disclosed by ASB.

**3\. Information ASB Collects**

(a) Personally Identifiable Information: Personal Information is information that could reasonably be used to identify you personally (such as your first and last name, gender, phone number, address, birth date, e-mail address, and, if applicable, your credit card information), which we refer to in this Policy as "PI." Generally, you may browse our Site without providing us with PI. However, there may be times when we ask you to provide us with certain PI, such as when you choose to register with our Site; post a photo, video, or message; or participate in e-commerce, interactive, or promotional activities. You can change or update your PI by changing your account information. We may also ask you to provide us with demographic information or information regarding your interests, hobbies or similar information to enhance your experience. ASB reserves the right, at any time, to add features to our Site that require you to register or otherwise provide additional PI. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in some of the Site's features. The PI you submit will be used to carry out your requests, respond to your inquiries, and to notify you (if applicable) regarding any promotions or e-commerce activities. Your PI may also be used by us and any parent, subsidiary, affiliate, joint venturer, sponsor and/or partner of ASB (collectively, “Affiliated Third Parties”) to provide you with additional services. You may always direct us by “opting-out” at the point where we ask for PI, and we will not share or use PI in order to provide you with additional services. However, if you do not want us to share this information, we may not be able to provide you with the additional services. In such case, please use our unsubscribe page and we will not share such information. We will not share PI with entities that are not Affiliated Third Parties unless you give us express permission to do so by opting-in at the point where we ask for PI. ASB does not sell, rent or share PI collected with other people other than that specifically outlined herein.

(b) This is not a Site directed to children under the age of 13 and ASB does not knowingly collect any information from children under 13 years of age at the Site. **If you are under 13 years of age, do not send any information about yourself to ASB.** If you are under 13 years of age, please do not use the ASB Site—there are lots of other great websites for you. Talk to your parents about what sites are appropriate for you.  If ASB learns that a child under the age of 13 has provided the Site with PI, ASB will delete that child's PI from its system.

(c) Anonymous Information: When you visit the Site, our web servers automatically collect Site usage information. Site usage information is anonymous information that describes how our visitors use and navigate our Site, and it includes the number and frequency of visitors to each web page, and the length of their stays. ASB collects the anonymous information automatically sent to us by your web browser, such as browser type, referrer data that identifies the web page visited prior and subsequent to visiting our Site, and IP address. We may also determine what technology is available through your browser in order to present you the most appropriate version of a web page (i.e. Flash or HTML).

(d) IP Addresses: When visitors request pages from our Site, our servers log the visitor's IP address. We may collect IP addresses for a variety of internal purposes, such as system administration, to report aggregate information to our business partners or to audit the number of visits to different pages, photos viewed or videos watched on our Site.

(e) Cookies: Cookies are small text files placed on your hard drive by a website when you visit. These files identify your computer and record your preferences and other data about your visit so that when you return to the Site, the Site knows who you are and can personalize your visit. In general, we use cookies to collect information so that we can determine how to improve the Site by seeing which areas, features and products are most popular, to personalize the Site and improve the Site experience. Most browsers automatically accept cookies as the default setting. You can modify the setting to reject cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit by editing browser options. If you decide not to accept our cookies, you will still be able to access those parts of our Site available to the general public but you may not be able to use some of the Site’s features or services and you may have a less satisfactory experience.    
We do not store any PI in cookies, but we may link the cookie to any information we collect. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers, which is standard in the Internet industry. We do not control these cookies, and these cookies are not subject to our privacy policy. Visitors to our Site should check the privacy policy of the advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. You can disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of the Site will not operate correctly if you disable cookies. You should consult with your browser's provider/manufacturer if you have any questions regarding disabling cookies.

**4\. ASB Use and Disclosure of Collected Information**

(a) ASB: ASB may use your PI to provide the information or content you have requested. We may also use your PI to contact you regarding your use of our Site or changes to our Policy or other policy or terms that affect you and your use of our Site. If you e-mail someone else a video, photo or other special feature from our Site, we may use the information you provide about someone else to send that person the requested e-mail. ASB may use information collected about our users to improve the Site’s content, design, navigation, or for other internal purposes such as analyzing aggregate traffic patterns and other trends.

(b) Third parties providing services on our behalf: ASB may employ other trusted companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include: 

(i) Third parties involved in analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service: These third parties may have access to our users' PI in order to provide these services to us on our behalf solely for such purposes.  However, they are not permitted to use PI for any other purpose. 

(ii) Third party providers of products and services:  We may disclose PI to third parties so they can inform you about their products or services. If you do not wish to receive these types of third party communications, you can click [here](http://www.airshowbuzz.com/contact.php) and complete a form to tell us your preferences. While you may choose not to receive direct marketing information from third parties, you will continue to receive marketing, promotional, and other information from ASB.

(c) Other Third Parties: ASB does not rent, sell or otherwise disclose your PI to third parties unless disclosed herein, or at the time such information is collected, or unless you otherwise give consent, other than in the following limited circumstances:

(i) Legal Action: ASB may disclose information about its users, including PI, when legally required to do so, for example at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Site and applicable laws, or to protest against misuse or unauthorized use of our Site. ASB may also disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability, to protect or defend our rights or property or protect the safety, rights or property of our users; 

(ii) Corporate Change: ASB may sell, transfer or otherwise disclose user information, including PI, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of all or substantially all assets, or other fundamental corporate change respecting ASB and/or the Site.

**5\. Third Party Websites**

Please be aware that we provide links to third party websites from the Site as a service to our guests and we are not responsible for the content, information collection, privacy policies or other use practices of those sites. Please also note that these websites' privacy policies will differ from those of ASB. Therefore, we encourage you to review and understand their privacy practices before providing them with information.

**6\. Security   **

ASB takes reasonable measures to secure the data you submit to us from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our user data. When possible, we will ask any third parties to whom we may transfer such information to take comparable measures. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, ASB cannot and does not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to ASB, and you do so at your own risk.

**7\. Consent to Transfer**

The Site is operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our Site, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.

**8\. Acceptance/Changes to Policy**

By using the Site, you agree to the terms of this Policy. ASB reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Policy at any time in its sole discretion. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back from time to time. We will only use the PI you provide to the Site in a manner consistent with our current Policy, unless you give us your consent.

**9\. Contact Us**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Policy, please contact us at [info@asb.tv](mailto:info@asb.tv "info@asb.tv"). Or you can send us mail to: 

3528 HAYDEN AVE  
SUITE P-51  
CULVER CITY, CA 90232.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
